Guide to the Book and Bond, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Membership Files, 1899-1934; Series II
  - Member files
    - Hayward, Albert Wyman, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Hill, Cyrus Giles, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Hill, Elton Brigham, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Hill, Francis William, active 1932 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Hill, Leslie Marshall, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Hills, Edward F., active 1932 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Hinckley, Edward Benjamin, active 1907 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Hitchcock, Melville Espe, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Horn, Sylvester Charles, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Houde, Robert Alfred, active 1934 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Houston, John Howard, active 1919 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Hume, George Sherwood, active 1916 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Hume, Walter Fairbank, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Hunsberger, Warren Seabury, active 1931 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Hunter, Ernest Carlisle, active 1913 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Hunting, Harold Bruce, active 1902 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Huntington, Andrew Sherwood, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Huntington, David Hull Sherwood, active 1912 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Immich, Hollis Douglass, active 1909 (as graduate student) (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Johnson, Stanley Todd, active 1916 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Johnstone, John Hamilton Lane, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Jonas, Charles Henry, active 1905 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Jones, Wayne Douglas, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Jordan, Richard Hawford, active 1931 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - Kaercher, George Hughes, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - Kavanagh, Ernest Sherwin, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - Keeling, Ralph Franklin, active 1924 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - Keeney, Joseph Sumner, active 1919 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Keeney, Russell James, active 1917 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Keller, Charles Roy, active 1920 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Kennan, Robert McCormick, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Kellogg, Hosford Dudley Jr., active 1920 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Kirby, Otis Edgar, active 1924 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Knapp, Forrest Lamar, active 1923 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Knowles, Noel Hugh, active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Kwai, Addison Yung, active 1923 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Kwai, Dana Yung, active 1923 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Kyger, Jack Adolphus, active 1933 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - LaMont, Charles Augustus, active 1904 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - Laslett, Basil George Frederick, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Law, Frank Erle, active 1905 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Lawrence, George Edward, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Leavenworth, Edward Kendrick, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Lee, Kenneth Ray, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Lee, Louis Emerson, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Lee, Mimms William, active 1912 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Legate, Ralph Holme, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - Leonard, Irving Albert, active 1916 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Lewis, George Albert, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Light, George Simmons, active 1926 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Lindeman, Herman Henry, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Lockhart, Charles Edwin, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Lockhart, Joseph Andrew, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Longwell, Chester Ray, active 1917 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Lockwood, Edwin Hoyt, honorary member 1911 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - Lovell, Richard Leonard, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Lyford, John III, active 1932 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - Lyman, John, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Lyman, Henry Hall, active 1908 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - MacKenzie, William Nelson, active 1913 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Macnie, John Percival, active 1919 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - Madigan, John Bertrand, active 1933 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Malone, Dumas, active 1915 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Martin, Azel Anson, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - Martin, Charles Francis, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - Martin, Francis Linton, active 1910 (Box 3, Folder 282)
    - Martson, Trowbridge, active 1904 (Box 3, Folder 283)
    - Maurer, Oscar Edward, active 1906 (Box 3, Folder 284)
    - Maurer, Oscar Edward Jr., active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 285)
    - Maurer, Washington Irving, active 1906 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    - Maurer, William Spooner, active 1928 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    - McBride, Gordon Williams, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    - McCann, William Sidney, active 1914 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    - McClare, John Kenneth, active 1925 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - McGovern, William Lawrence, active 1933 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - McGuire, Ritchie Quincy Victor, active 1920 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - McKown, Arthur Wesley, active 1929 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - McMillan, William Thomas Jr., active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - McMurray, Murray, active 1911 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - McNulty, Raymond Peter, active 1906 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    - McQuary, Rodney L., active 1913 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    - McQueeney, Andrew Joseph, active 1934 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    - McTighe, James Norbert, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    - Mershon, Harry Grant, active 1916 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    - Merwin, Royal Andrews, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 301)
    - Miles, Arthur Dorland, active 1904 (Box 3, Folder 302)
    - Miller, Paul Lathorp, active 1906 (Box 3, Folder 303)
    - Mitchell, Philip Henry, active 1904 (Box 3, Folder 304)
    - Monjo, George L., active 1933 (Box 3, Folder 305)
    - Moore, Lawrence Cecil, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 306)
    - Morehouse, Harold Edgar Jr., active 1931 (Box 3, Folder 307)
    - Morgan, Frederick Edward, active 1909 (Box 3, Folder 308)
    - Morse, Edmund Cooper, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 309)
    - Morse, Jarvis Means, active 1920 (Box 3, Folder 310)
    - Morse, Walter Ronald, active 1907 (Box 3, Folder 311)
    - Morton, Sydney Byron, active 1903 (Box 3, Folder 312)
    - Moyle, Edgerton Lee, active 1921 (Box 3, Folder 313)
    - Munsche, Richard Charles Jr., active 1932 (Box 3, Folder 314)
    - Nead, Benjamin Frank II, charter member n.d. (Box 3, Folder 315)
    - Nead, Benjamin Matthias, honorary member n.d. (Box 3, Folder 316)
    - Nead, Robert Hayes, active 1901 (Box 3, Folder 317)
    - Newcomb, James Edward, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 318)
    - Nightwine, Lennie Shell, active 1913 (Box 3, Folder 319)
    - North, Herbert Brickerhoff, charter member n.d. (Box 3, Folder 320)
    - North, Richard Alden, active 1918 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - North, Walter Frederick, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Norton, Edward Hodges, active 1909 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Norton, John Albion, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Norton, William Bunnell, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    - Oviatt, Eugene Frederick, active 1931 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    - Otwell, Percy Clinton, active 1911 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - Owens, Howard D., active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - Parkinson, Edward William Brown, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - Parry, Marion Henry, active 1924 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - Parsons, Frederick Austin Jr., active 1919 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Patterson, Burton Bull, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Perley, Alden Dun, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Perry, Sherman Hickox, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - Pettit, George Emerson, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - Pettyjohn, Wallace Hogarth, active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 336)
    - Phillips, Byron Stevens, active 1915 (Box 4, Folder 337)
    - Pierson, Adrian Abraham, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 338)
    - Pitt, Arthur Stewart, active 1933 (Box 4, Folder 339)
    - Pond, Dwight Cameron, active 1932 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Porter, Hezekiah Scovil, active 1917 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Porter, Howard Park, active 1909 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    - Powell, Thomas Benjamin, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 343)
    - Pratt, Dudley, active 1916 (Box 4, Folder 344)
    - Prentice, Donald Bishop, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 345)
    - Prudden, Theodore Mitchell, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 346)
    - Purcell, Joseph Frederic, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 347)
    - Quiggin, George Robert, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 348)
    - Rand, Eben Eaton, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 349)
    - Ray, J. Franklin Jr., active 1924 (Box 4, Folder 350)
    - Read, Harry Hollister, charter member n.d. (Box 4, Folder 351)
    - Read, Robert Wright, active 1901 (Box 4, Folder 352)
    - Reed, Myron George, active 1916 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    - Remington, Frederic, honorary member 1901 (Box 4, Folder 354)
    - Rew, Robert E. Jr., active 1933 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - Rice, John Pierrepont, active 1901 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    - Richardson, Leroy Mowry, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    - Riley, Robert Annan, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    - Robbins, Alfred Newton, active 1903 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    - Roberts, Charles Asaph, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    - Robinson, Heath Montgomery, active 1914 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Robinson, Monroe Lafferty, active 1924 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    - Rogers, Burton Bush, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 363)
    - Rogers, Philip, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 364)
    - Rohne, Chester Summers, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 365)
    - Rossiter, Ivan Seymour, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 366)
    - Rouse, Beekman Oliver, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Rouse, Benjamin Irving, active 1932 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    - Rudd, Charles Edward, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    - Rush, Lowell Palmer, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    - Rush, Raymond Warren, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Russ, Charles Cooke, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Russ, Henry Camp, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Rutledge, Orrin Clark, active 1929 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Sanford, Davis Sammis Jr., active 1922 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Sanford, Donald Wetherell, active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Saunders, Francis Alexander, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Scheller, Oswald Paul, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Schlegal, Wilfred Balthas, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 379)
    - Schnelle, Charles Stephen, active 1929 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Schulze, Herman Frederick Benjamin, active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - Schumpert, Robert Lee, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Schweickher, Frederick William, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - Scott, Leroy Ellsworth, active 1916 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Scott, Ralph Edward, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Scudder, Lawrence Williams, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - Seltzer, Daniel, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Sexton, Frederick Lester, active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Seybolt, Allen Upson, active 1930 (Box 4, Folder 389)
    - Shattuck, Angelo Eusebius, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Shattuck, Howard Francis, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Shepard, Francis Henry Jr., active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Shepherd, Roswell Linsley, active 1917 (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Stanley, Sherburn Moore, active 1934 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Sherlock, Frank Theodore, active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Shields, George Kendall, active 1909 (Box 4, Folder 396)
    - Shotts, Claude Cornelius, active 1922 (Box 4, Folder 397)
    - Schultes, Edwin Matthias III, active 1929 (Box 4, Folder 398)
    - Sikes, Franklin Victory, active 1901 (Box 4, Folder 399)
    - Simpson, Frederick Thomas, honorary member 1901 (Box 4, Folder 400)
    - Slattery, Frank John, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 401)
    - Small, Edwin Williams, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 402)
    - Smith, Allan Oakley, active 1909 (Box 4, Folder 403)
    - Smith, Alzamora Burdette, active 1914 (Box 4, Folder 404)
    - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, honorary member 1913 (Box 4, Folder 405)
    - Smith, Harold Ellsworth, active 1909 (Box 4, Folder 406)
    - Smith, John Owen, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 407)
    - Sneath, George Mark, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 408)
    - Snee, James Joseph Marion, active 1917 (Box 4, Folder 409)
    - Somers, William Hill, active 1914 (Box 4, Folder 410)
    - Speer, Gareth Wright, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 411)
    - Speer, John Howard, active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 412)
    - Squires, Edwin Burrett Jr., active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 413)
    - Steinecke, William Matthew, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 414)
    - Stetson, Joseph Kusterer, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 415)
    - Stevens, Clement Douglass, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 416)
    - Stevens, Harry Nelson, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 417)
    - Stewart, Charles Lyman, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 418)
    - Stilson, Minott Auger Osborn Jr., active 1929 (Box 4, Folder 419)
    - Stockmeyer, Harry Stephen, active 1920 (Box 4, Folder 420)
    - Stuart, Burton Baldwin, active 1931 (Box 4, Folder 421)
    - Stunkel, Francis Henry, active 1919 (Box 4, Folder 422)
    - Sullivan, Raymond Florence, active 1918 (Box 4, Folder 423)
    - Sutherland, Earl William, active 1915 (Box 4, Folder 424)
    - Swanson, Hilding Alfred, active 1911 (Box 4, Folder 425)
    - Swayne, Noah Haynes III, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 426)
    - Swift, Charles Lowe, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 427)
    - Swift, Gordon Clarke, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 428)
    - Sylvester, E. Paul, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 429)
    - Taggart, Robert, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 430)
    - Talcott, Louis Hart, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 431)
    - Talcott, Morris Gardner, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 432)
    - Taylor, Edwy Lycurgus, charter member 1900 (Box 4, Folder 433)
    - Taylor, Samuel Bartram Richards, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 434)
    - Teeple, John Alexander, active 1930 (Box 4, Folder 435)
    - Templeton, Roger John, active 1918 (Box 4, Folder 436)
    - Tennant, Richard Grenville, active 1917 (Box 4, Folder 437)
    - Tennant, Robert Jr., active 1924 (Box 4, Folder 438)
    - Thomas, Edward Utley, active 1933 (Box 4, Folder 439)
    - Thomas, Glenn R., active 1933 (Box 4, Folder 440)
    - Thompson, Franklin V., active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 441)
    - Thompson, Fred Hodgdon, graduate member 1906 (Box 4, Folder 442)
    - Thompson, James Stanley, active 1922 (Box 4, Folder 443)
    - Thompson, Philip Russell, active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 444)
    - Thompkins, George Ira, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 445)
    - Tompkins, Harry Warren, active 1901 (Box 4, Folder 446)
    - Tisdale, Lincoln Cody, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 447)
    - Toomey, Philip Arthur, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 448)
    - Tracy, Frederick Erwin, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 449)
    - Trotter, Reginald George, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 450)
    - Troxell, Edward Leffingwell, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 451)
    - Truesdell, Robert Fuller, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 452)
    - Turck, Harlow Ellsworth, active 1923 (Box 4, Folder 453)
    - Turkington, Charles Henry, active 1902 (Box 4, Folder 454)
    - Turner, Maxwell, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 455)
    - Tuttle, Bruce Rothrock, active 1920 (Box 4, Folder 456)
    - Tyler, William Finney, active 1905 (Box 4, Folder 457)
    - Vail, Ramon Montgomery, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 458)
    - Vail, Thorton Edwin, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 459)
    - Van Blarcom, Dixon, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 460)
    - Van Brunt, Elmer Willis, active 1903 (Box 4, Folder 461)
    - Van Brunt, Rulif Seely, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 462)
    - Vanderburgh, Alexander, active 1919 (Box 4, Folder 463)
    - Veale, William Henry, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 464)
    - Vidal, Howard Andrew, graduate member 1906 (Box 4, Folder 465)
    - Von der Sump, Frederick Herman, active 1912 (Box 4, Folder 466)
    - Wakeman, Alfred Maurice, active 1916 (Box 4, Folder 467)
    - Wakeman, Edward Taylor, active 1916 (Box 4, Folder 468)
    - Wallis, John, active 1926 (Box 4, Folder 469)
    - Warfield, George Kenneth, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 470)
    - Warren, Charles R., active 1933 (Box 4, Folder 471)
    - Warren, Ernest Ross, active 1907 (Box 4, Folder 472)
    - Waters, Hardy Stone, active 1911 (Box 4, Folder 473)
    - Wells, Ralph Olney, active 1900 (Box 4, Folder 474)
    - Welton, Leonard Herschel, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 475)
    - Westcott, John Benjamin, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 476)
    - Weston, Rolfe Arthur Jr., active 1919 (Box 4, Folder 477)
    - Wetherill, William Henry, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 478)
    - Wittenberg, Robert Binghurst, active 1922 (Box 4, Folder 479)
    - Wheeler, Rufus Arthur, active 1925 (Box 4, Folder 480)
    - White, Herbert Palmer, active 1927 (Box 4, Folder 481)
    - Whittemore, Lewis Bliss, active 1904 (Box 4, Folder 482)
    - Wilcox, Reynold Webb, honorary member 1901 (Box 4, Folder 483)
    - Williams, Frank Sargood Geils, active 1922 (Box 4, Folder 484)
    - Wilson, George Campbell, active 1924 (Box 4, Folder 485)
    - Wilson, Maple, active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 486)
    - Wilson, Leon Thomas, active 1920 (Box 4, Folder 487)
    - Wintermute, Edwin Hampton, active 1920 (Box 4, Folder 488)
    - Wolff, Frederick Merwin, active 1931 (Box 4, Folder 489)
    - Wood, Charles Doris, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 490)
    - Wood, Frances Marion, active 1928 (Box 4, Folder 491)
    - Woods, Robert Pirrie, active 1932 (Box 4, Folder 492)
    - Woodward, Samuel Austin, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 493)
    - Workman, George Bell, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 494)
    - Workman, James Warthen, active 1921 (Box 4, Folder 495)
    - Wrenshall, Richard, active 1910 (Box 4, Folder 496)
    - Wright, Cecil, active 1906 (Box 4, Folder 497)
    - Wright, Edwin Kingsbury, active 1930 (Box 4, Folder 498)
    - Wright, Morgan Spencer, active 1919 (Box 4, Folder 499)
    - Wright, Selah Howell, graduate member 1907 (Box 4, Folder 500)
    - Wyckoff, Spofford Frank, active 1908 (Box 4, Folder 501)
    - Yale, Allen Rice, active 1929 (Box 4, Folder 502)
    - Yates, Clyde Raymond, active 1913 (Box 4, Folder 503)
    - Yost, Howard Simpson, active 1931 (Box 4, Folder 504)
- Accession 2006-A-087
  - Abridged constitution and paddle, Circa 1901-1930 (Box 1)